G. D. Hsiung papers
Medical Historical Library, Harvey Cushing / John Hay Whitney Medical Library
- Yale School of Medicine, Department of Laboratory Medicine, Series III
  - Laboratory Medicine Residency Program, 1977-1988; Subseries 2
    G. D. Hsiung took part in the "Yale-VA Integrated Clinical Pathology Residency Program." Residents in Laboratory Medicine participated in conferences and symposia held both at Yale School of Medicine and at the VA Hospital in West Haven. Residents did a rotation at the VA Hospital. Folders may include the names of residents, a list of lectures for residents, and information on what residents needed to learn.
    - Residency Program, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Residency Program, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Residency Program, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Residency Program, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Residency Program, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Residency Program, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Contains a copy of "Department of Laboratory Medicine, Resident Review of the Residency Program, 1987-1988," with Hsiung's comments in pencil.
    - Residency Program, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Residency Program, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Residency Program, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Post-doctoral Fellows, Subseries 3
    - List of past and present Post-Doctoral Fellows, 1962-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      Presumably these were post-doctoral fellows at Yale or associated institutions. The list was organized by year of training period, including each fellow's name and degrees, source of support, and current position.
    - "Residents and Postdoctoral Fellows in Clinical Laboratories for 1980-81", 1980 July 8 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      Brief biographical information on seven individuals including birth date, degrees, and former positions.
    - Postdoctoral fellows, 1985-1986, 1986-1987, and 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Wallace Rowe Clinical Virology Lectureship, 1983-1990; Subseries 4
    Wallace P. Rowe (1926-1983) was a pioneer in clinical virology, "internationally known for his research on the molecular biology and genetics of tumor viruses and recombinant DNA." He had lectured in the post-graduate course in clinical virology at Yale since 1966. A clinical virology symposium was held honoring him on September 15, 1983. An annual lecture series at Yale was established in his name in 1985 with funding by the Vicks Research Center, Shelton, Conn. Hsiung played a major role in founding the lecture seies and she introduced the earliest lecturers.
    - Correspondence, 1983, and biographical material on Wallace Rowe (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Wallace Rowe Clinical Virology Lectureship, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      The first annual lecture was given by Jack Gwaltney, Jr. on November 8, 1985. The folder includes a lecture poster, Hsiung's introduction of the speaker, and Hsiung's correspondence, 1985.
    - Wallace Rowe Clinical Virology Lectureship, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      The second Wallace Rowe Lecture was presented on March 20, 1987 by Richard Colonno, M.D. The folder contains the poster for the lecture, Hsiung's introduction, her correspondence, 1986-1987, and the CV of the speaker.
    - Wallace Rowe Clinical Virology Lecture, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      The third Wallace Rowe lecture was presented by Martin S. Hirsch, M.D. on November 9, 1990. The folder contains correspondence of Hsiung and John Booss, and the lecture poster.
  - Other Yale-related, Subseries 5
    - Medical Student-Faculty Advisor Program, 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      The folder contains administrative materials on the program. The faculty member was to serve as an advisor "to an incoming first-year student through his or her term in the School of Medicine." Hsiung was an advisor to Susan Baserga, Class of 1984, and now a faculty member.
    - Laboratory Medicine faculty retreat, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Contains memoranda, an agenda, and Hsiung's notes for a Department of Laboratory Medicine retreat at the Inn at Chester, May 20, 1988.
    - Agenda and minutes of the Board of Permanent Officers, 1989 May 17 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      The Board of Permanent Officers was a faculty/administrative committee of the Yale School of Medicine.
    - Yale Animal Care and Use Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      Memorandum from the Yale Provost, Edward A. Adelbert, to "All principal investigators using vertebrate animals in their research," containing guidelines, and how to refer inquiries by animal rights activists. Hsiung filled out a form stating that she and Brigitte Griffith were using 1000 guinea pigs.
- Veterans Administration Medical Center, West Haven, Series IV
  - Internal memoranda by G. D. Hsiung and others, 1974-1990; Subseries 1
    This subseries contains internal memoranda by G.D. Hsiung as Chief of the Virology Laboratory. Some are directed to higher-up staff, reporting on the work of the laboratory or on the need for supplies and personnel. Others are memos to her staff. There is also material on the Research and Education Committee of the Veterans Administration Medical Center, West Haven.
    - Memoranda, Diagnostic Services of the Clinical Virology Laboratory, 1974-1979 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Memoranda, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda, 50th Anniversary of the VAMC, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Contains Hsiung's memoranda to Dr. Philip Bondy on "the contributions of my research program and those of the Virology Laboratory to the Veteran's Administration," and a draft of "Summary of Dr. Hsiung's Research Accomplishments."
    - Memoranda, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Form letters for postdoctoral applicants (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Form letters to answer inquiries about post-doctoral fellowships at the VA, and rejection letters for unsuccessful applicants. The folder also contains diagrams of the organization of the Virology Laboratory.
  - Medical Virology Seminar, Subseries 2
    The Medical Virology Seminar was held weekly at the VA. Some of the weeks were devoted to the Journal Club and others to presentations. Folders contain lists of dates and speakers.
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Medical Virology Seminar, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - VAMC Annual Investigator Reports, Subseries 3
    This sub-series contains G. D. Hsiung's annual reports to the VA Research and Development Information System, a computerized system for information about VA investigators. Hsiung's report contains lists of lectures presented and publications. Reports may contain information on the number and kinds of animals used. But the reports do not contain narrative accounts of the work of the laboratory.
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Annual Investigator Report, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Subseries 4
    - Budget, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Budget, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Budget, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Budget, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Merit Reviews of VA-Funded Research Projects, 1967-1990; Subseries 5
    These are merit reviews within the VA for funding for research projects. Folders contain proposals, reviews, occasional correspondence, and reports. There may be some overlap with Annual Reports. Folders may contain Social Security numbers.
    - Latent virus infections in human and non-human tissues, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Latent virus Infections and viral oncogenicity--Proposal, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Latent virus infections and viral oncogenicity--Renewal, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Studies of latent virus infections and viral oncogenicity--Proposal, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Latent virus infections and viral oncogenicity--Proposal, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Latent virus infections and viral oncogenicity, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - The role of latent viruses as pathogens and oncogens--Proposal, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Effect of antiviral agents on genital herpes infection, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Multiple herpesvirus infections in an immunocompromised model--Correspondence and proposal, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Multiple herpesvirus infections in an immunocompromised model--Narrative, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Viral interactions in an immunocompromised model, 1982-1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Viral interactions in an immunocompromised model--Proposal, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Viral interactions in an immunocompromised model, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Serologic analysis of CMV and HTLV-III antibody status - Report, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Dual infections with cytomegalovirus and retrovirus--Proposal, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Dual infections with cytomegalovirus and retrovirus--Response to review (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Grants, Subseries 6
    - List of Grants and Contracts, 1971-1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "The Relationship of Herpesvirus Hominis to Oral Cancer" (P.I. Norman Swack, VA Hospital), 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      A collaborative project on studies of antibody titers in humans to Herpes Simplex Types 1 and 2
    - Grant Proposal to NIH: "Genital Herpes: Effect on Mother and Offspring" by Marie L. Landry. M.D., 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      Marie Landry worked in Hsiung's laboratory at the VA. The proposal was recommended for approval but not funded.
    - Grant proposal to NIH: "Experimental Models for CMV Infections" (2 RO1-HD10609-04) P.I. G.D. Hsiung, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Grant proposal to NIH: "Experimental Models for CMV Infections" (2 RO1-HD10609-08) P.I. Frank Bia, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - NIH Grant: "Chemotherapy of HIV Infection: Ultrastructural Approaches (1 RO1 AI28241-01A1) P.I. G.D. Hsiung, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - NIH Grant: "Chemotherapy of HIV Infection: Ultrastructural Approaches" (5 RO1 AI28241-03), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - NIH Grant "Chemotherapy of HIV Infection: Ultrastructural Approaches" (5 RO1 AI28241-03), 1991 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - NIH Grant "Chemotherapy of HIV Infection: Ultrastructural Approaches" (5 RO1 AI28241-03), 1992 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - NIH Contracts, Subseries 7
    - Collaborative Antiviral Testing Group Annual Meeting, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      This NIH-sponsored group of contractors, known as the Collaborative Antiviral Testing Group, met annually at NIH. Their meetings were held conjunction with the CMV contractors meeting, also involving G. D. Hsiung, for "developing antiviral drugs for the treatment of cytomegalovirus infections." Both groups were concerned with developing animal models for testing.
    - Collaborative Antiviral Testing Group Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Collaborative Antiviral Testing Group Annual Meeting, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Collaborative Antiviral Testing Group Annual Meeting, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Collaborative Antiviral Testing Group Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - NIH Connecticut Regional Meeting, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      This was a regional forum in conjunction with NIH strategic planning.
    - RFP-NIH-NIAID-MIDP-82-9, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      Hsiung's proposal, "Multiple Herpesvirus Infections in an Immunocompromised Model," was in response to an NIH RFP (Request for proposal) under the heading, "Application of Biophysical, Biochemical, Immunologic, and Molecular Virologic Techniques to Rapid Viral Diagnosis." Folder includes photographs.
    - RFP-NIH-NIAID-MIDP-86-4, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Hsiung's proposal for the project "Animal Models for Antiviral Evaluation" was in response to an NIH RFP. She obtained the contract N01-A1-62519.
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1985-May 30, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1985-November 30, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1986-November 30, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for April !987-December 1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1987-November 30, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for May 1, 1988-April 30, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for May 1, 1989-December 1, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1989-May 1, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1989-November 30, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1990-July 30, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Report for December 1, 1990-November 30, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - NIH Contract NOI-AI-62519, Final Technical Report, December 30, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - RFP NIH-NIAID-DMID-91-02, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      This was a proposal in response to an NIH RFP under the title "Animal Models of Human Viral Infections for Evaluation of Experimental Therapeutics." Hsiung's proposal was titled "Guinea pig model of cytomegalovirus infections for evaluation of experimental therapeutics." The folder contains responses and a request for a revised proposal.
  - Diagnostic Virology Postgraduate Courses/Workshops, 1962-1979; Subseries 8
    Diagnostic Virology was a course offered to graduate students and post-doctoral fellows from 1962-1979.
    - Overview of Diagnostic Virology Courses, 1962-1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Contains the title of the course, names of participants, and notes.
    - Diagnostic Virology Course: Curriculum/Participants, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      This was a two-week summer postgraduate course taught at Yale and directed by G. D. Hsiung. Those who were qualified to take the course could apply from around the country to attend. Folder includes a photograph of participants.
    - Diagnostic Virology Course: Curriculum/Participants, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      This was also a summer course with a variety of students, mostly not from Yale.
    - Diagnostic Virology Course: Lectures, Part I, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Full typed text of lecture(s) with photographs pasted in.
    - Diagnostic Virology Course: Lectures, Part II, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Diagnostic Virology Course: Curriculum/Participants, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Includes unidentified snapshots of students and teachers, some taken at a barbecue.
    - Diagnostic Virology Course: Curriculum/Participants, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Also includes a photograph of a man teaching the class and reviews by students of the course.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      This summer seminar was sponsored by the New York University Post-Graduate School of Medicine and the Veterans Administration Hospital, New York, N.Y. Folder includes a photograph of participants and unidentified small headshots.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Handwritten notes.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Mostly handwritten notes.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      This summer seminar was also sponsored by the New York University Post-Graduate School of Medicine and the Veterans Administration Hospital, New York, N.Y. The folder contains photographs of participants and course reviews by students.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      This seminar was taught at Yale in May 1968 and sponsored by the Yale University School of Medicine and the Veterans Administration Hospital, West Haven. Folder includes the curriculum, applications, course reviews, and photographs of the students and teachers.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Folder contains formal and informal photographs of the class and faculty. The 1970 course was conducted in May at the VA Diagnostic Virology Laboratory in West Haven.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      The 1971 course was conducted in November at the Diagnostic Virology Laboratory.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Diagnostic Virology 10th Anniversary Reunion, 1971 November 11-12 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      A reunion dinner for earlier participants was held at the Veterans Administration Hospital on November 11, with more speakers and a round-table on November 12. Dr. J. L. Melnick and Dr. W. P. Rowe were speakers. The folder contains correspondence, names of the participants, the program, and snapshots.
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      The 1973 course was held in October and sponosred by the Tissue Culture Association, Inc. Continuing Education Program, Yale University School of Medicine, and the Veterans Administration Hospital, West Haven. It took place in the W. Alton Jones Cell Science Center, Lake Placid, New York.
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Participants, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Contains the applications, the participants, a group photo with everyone identified, and snapshots.
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Presentations by Participants, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      This course was held September 30-October 11, 1974 at the W. Alton Jones Cell Science Center, Lake Placid, New York.
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Participants, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Applications, photographs, list of student reports, and comments and suggestions by participants.
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      The 1977 course was held in June at the Veterans Administration Hospital, West Haven and was co-sponsored by Yale University School of Medicine. See also photo notebook in Box 35.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Participants, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Lectures, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Curriculum/Participants, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      This was a course or symposium held at the VA from June 18-29, 1979, and featured lectures open to physicians and staff. The folder contains a list of participants, a list of lectures, formal and informal photographs, and a newspaper article featuring two scientists from China who attended the course. More photographs can be found in Box 35.
    - Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology: Laboratory Exercises, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Virology Reference Laboratory, 1977-1993; Series V
  The Virology Reference Laboratory (VRL) at the VA was created through the efforts of G.D. Hisung. It stemmed from Hsiung's Virology Laboratory at the VA, supported by VA funds and NIH research funds administered through the Yale School of Medicine. As advances were made in identifying viruses and offering targeted therapy for viral infections, Hsiung hoped that a central VA laboratory in West Haven could serve other VA Hospitals around the country. The VRL would identify viral isolates from specimens sent in by other VA Hospitals. In the early 1980s, a survey of VA Hospitals was undertaken to assess the need of such a service (see Box 18). Hsiung was granted a trial period for a year in 1984, and in 1985 the VRL was officially established through approval and funding by the VA. Hsiung became the first director of the VRL. The VRL did research projects in addition to handling specimens. The staff investigated combination therapies used against cytomegalorvirus and HIV. After Hsiung's retirement, Dr. Marie Landry became director.
  - Proposal and operation of the VRL, 1979-1993; Subseries 1
    - Proposal for a central VA viral diagnostic laboratory, 1977 January 19 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Separated Materials
      Includes a reprint of M. L. Landry and G. D. Hsiung, "The Virus Diagnostic Laboratory: Its Function in a VA Medical Center," Connecticut Medicine 45[7] (July 1981): 417-422, which was sent to all VA laboratories in the country.
    - Proposal draft, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Clinical Virology Reference Laboratory, 1983 January (Box 17, Folder 4)